[
	{
		"question": "0.How to see all docker networks?",
		"answer": "docker network ls",
		"answerType": "terminal",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":0
	},
	{
		"question": "1.What variables can be set for array reduce?",
		"answer": "array.reduce((previousValue, currentValue, currentIndex, array) => {  /* ... */  }, initialValue)",
		"answerType": "javascript",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":1
	},
	{
		"question": "2.What's on the first line of a docker-compose file?",
		"answer": "version: '3.8'",
		"answerType": "yaml",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":2
	},{
		"question": "3.How to see all docker networks?",
		"answer": "docker network ls",
		"answerType": "terminal",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":3
	},
	{
		"question": "4.What variables can be set for array reduce?",
		"answer": "array.reduce((previousValue, currentValue, currentIndex, array) => {  /* ... */  }, initialValue)",
		"answerType": "javascript",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":4
	},
	{
		"question": "5.What's on the first line of a docker-compose file?",
		"answer": "version: '3.8'",
		"answerType": "yaml",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":5
	},{
		"question": "6.How to see all docker networks?",
		"answer": "docker network ls",
		"answerType": "terminal",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":6
	},
	{
		"question": "7.What variables can be set for array reduce?",
		"answer": "array.reduce((previousValue, currentValue, currentIndex, array) => {  /* ... */  }, initialValue)",
		"answerType": "javascript",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":7
	},
	{
		"question": "8.What's on the first line of a docker-compose file?",
		"answer": "version: '3.8'",
		"answerType": "yaml",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":8
	},{
		"question": "9.How to see all docker networks?",
		"answer": "docker network ls",
		"answerType": "terminal",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":9
	},
	{
		"question": "10.What variables can be set for array reduce?",
		"answer": "array.reduce((previousValue, currentValue, currentIndex, array) => {  /* ... */  }, initialValue)",
		"answerType": "javascript",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":10
	},
	{
		"question": "11.What's on the first line of a docker-compose file?",
		"answer": "version: '3.8'",
		"answerType": "yaml",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":11
	},{
		"question": "12.How to see all docker networks?",
		"answer": "docker network ls",
		"answerType": "terminal",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":12
	},
	{
		"question": "13.What variables can be set for array reduce?",
		"answer": "array.reduce((previousValue, currentValue, currentIndex, array) => {  /* ... */  }, initialValue)",
		"answerType": "javascript",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":13
	},
	{
		"question": "14.What's on the first line of a docker-compose file?",
		"answer": "version: '3.8'",
		"answerType": "yaml",
		"streak": 0,
        "id":14
	}
]
